(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-18T12:53:18.648808",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Hi.
I thought I was gonna burp,
and then I thought, "Imagine if the first thing I say when I meet you is just a burp."
and then I thought, "Imagine if the first thing I say when I meet you guys is just a burp."
That would have been quite... That would have been something.
Anyway, hi!
Hi!
Ah...
Hi.
I... I was...
Can you hear me over this jazz band?
Let me calm down... let me calm down the brass real quick.
Oh, is it fine?
Give me—
Ah!
Hello! Is my birthday today?
What was I going to say? Oh, I was going to say, I was so nervous before...
the start of the stream, I was just saying "Ah" into my microphone like that, but like really quietly and like sensually—
well not sensually, I was just saying it quietly.
Oh, and I was listening to my heart beat so loud and so hard, uh, you can hear it, I can like hear it in my throat.
That's kind of gross, isn't it?
Ew, did you know there's a skeleton inside you right now?
And next to the skeleton, there's like hearts and stuff.
Did you know there's like squishy pieces inside you?
There's a skeleton living inside you!
And he has a collection of other squishy things. Ew.
I'm also, or I'm incredibly fidgety today because I'm so nervous.
Anyway, today is my birthday!
is it that?
Happy birthday to me!
I'm 9,303.
I look like a baby.
Um, but I
I can't rhyme with E.
Okay, just making sure.
This is pretty recorded? No.
Sucks to suck!
I'm sorry, I can't say that.
I can't be just...
I can't be
I can't be like that already.
I'm sorry, I'm a bit on the... Um, I'm gonna bite you.
Don't say anything mean to me.
I'm I'm into my birthday.
Do you see this face when you're bullying me?
This is the face you're bullying.
Do you see this?
How could you?
This is what you're being mean to.
Can't bully the birthday girl. It's not fair.
Or is it that you can only bully someone on their birthday?
Well, technically bullying, I guess, is a bit it hits it hits a bit harder when it's your birthday.
Oh, my goodness, do we have stuff to do? Do I have the not the brain for it?
So much to do, so little brain space.
So little brain activity.
I can't hear over the jazz band, but you guys seem to be okay with it.
I just want to say thank you guys for coming.
Thank you for being here. Thank you for all of my birthday wishes that I saw on Twitter and all of you here saying happy birthday.
Thank you so much.
All right, chill out, jazz.
Thank you guys.
I really do appreciate it.
It makes me feel very warm and fuzzy.
I was having a chat with uh uh who said, Stafan? Man, Monday's on.
Element management. And I was talking about how how easy it is for me to cry, especially on my birthday. I was like, oh boy.
Because they came to me and they were like, girl, you know you have you have uh we got a we got a gift for you from
quite a few ebbys, and I said, oh, oh no,
is this is this going to be my my big cry?
My big uncon unconsolable my unconsolable my big inconsolable cry session on stream.
It's like almost every year I have at least one at least one big cryfest cuz I'm a big baby.
I'm a big cry baby and that's okay.
That's okay.
Oh my god, I forgot to tell you about my birthday cake.
So, uh, my birthday cake, can you guess what kind of cake it is?
Hmm, I got a...
Oh, don't guess, I'm gonna tell you.
I got a strawberry cake. It's got like uh whipped cream and strawberries. Did you guess? Yeah, strawberries.
My favorite, my favorite. I could eat my weight in strawberries in like two hours.
Give me two hours and I'll eat the entire thing of strawberries.
Yeah. Also, do you see your little...
Do you see this? This little emojis on the side?
I can see all your emojis, so if all you guys put in the poopoo emoji,
it would just be a stream of poopoo.
But I'm seeing a lot of what do I see? Hearts, 100,
like cute stuff. I don't think the custom emojis go through though.
But yeah, hello. Thank you.
Thank you for the hellos and the happy birthdays.
Happy birthday, happy birthday.
Ah, one year older.
Isn't that weird to think about?
See, the problem on my birthday is I start to do a little too much deep thinking and next thing you know I'm spiraling.
Like, oh, I'm birthday, and then you think about the planet, and then the spinning of the planet, and then all of the planets, and then I start thinking about UFOs.
And then I freaked myself out really badly and I had to go to bed.
Do you ever do that? Don't let the brain run too far, because sometimes it runs down really scary places.
Oh boy, what do we have planned for today?
Um, I guess we could, we could take a peek at the birthday gift that uh a big group of you worked on for me.
I won't cry, I promise I won't cry. Thank you for promise.
And then afterwards, um I have some gifts for you because...
It's, think of it like a goody bag.
Do you guys remember getting goody bags when you went to birthday?
Oh wait! Oh my god, I forgot to tell you about that.
Do you remember...
Do you remember when you were a little baby,
and you would get like catalogs in the mail, and they would have themed character birthday party packs?
I was looking I was looking them up
because I really wanted to do one, don't judge me, but I really wanted to do one.
And I was thinking like, oh, kids these days,
I bet you she like uh, they're probably still like
little princesses and like Barbie and like Hot Wheels.
And I was thinking, oh, Bluey and stuff like that.
And you know what? They still have them.
I didn't do it this year, but maybe next year
I'll throw myself a Bluey birthday party.
Bluey the dog, yeah, because I can, and that's the magic of it.
So if you want to do that for your birthday, I think you should do it.
You should get a piñata too, and beat it up.
What was I saying though? Oh, oh yeah, reminding me.
Because you used to do like goody bags when you went to birthday parties, like in school and stuff.
That was like the best part, when you go to the birthday party and you give a gift, but then you get the goody bag at the end, it's got like a tattoo and a slap bracelet.
So think of my gifts to you as your goody bag.
Yeah.
Also, I always forget I like, I keep forgetting that I have to let myself breathe, but I don't like the silence of when I'm breathing, it makes me wildly uncomfortable.
But if I don't swallow and I don't breathe, then I won't be able to talk anymore.
Somebody somebody flick me in the forehead and tell me that's just don't do that, just breathe.
A gura bag, a goo a gooby bag.
I put my goo in it.
Tasty, I guess, tasty, I think.
Uh okay, so a gift to me, um, from a very large large group of you is here, I have it here, we're going to take a we're going to take a walk through it.
It is nearly 200 pages from what I can see.
I don't think we have time to go through all 200 pages, but
It's it's it's it's called Neuman Around the World, Wish You Were Here, and these look like all postcards. Do you see my cursor? No, okay.
Oh, sorry by the way, I had to cover you guys up, I apologize.
So, I want to see what this is. I went this far because it told me how to view it. Thank you very much, this is actually really helpful.
So, uh, hello, hola, bonjour, guten tag, ciao, konnichiwa, nihao, and how do you do? Chumbies from all around the world braved the most difficult challenge just for you. They touched grass.
Wow! Did you bring me back any?
Mmm, grass. It was no easy feat, but with a little Goomba by their side that gathered the courage to make this one-of-a-kind book, a group of dedicated everys were able to take the valiant efforts of your international community and make this travel journal be filled with breathtaking scenery, interesting attraction spots, and silly Goomba sightings.
I'm very excited. We hope we can give you the feeling as if you actually traveled to these places, perhaps even give you motivation and ideas for your next trip. Let's enjoy this amazing world together, the GGT team.
Travel journal and message screeners by Zame, Paul, Jeffrey and Reem. Communication and translation, Zame. Zame, Zefy, Bree, Pong, and LNYT. Hi guys!
Our graphic design book logo is by Shkissadorf, front and back covers by Adventure.
This is pretty cool. North America. Is it like postcards? Claus!
Artwork based on Lake Louise. Louise? Or is that a, see, the problem is now is you're going to really get to see how much I can't read.
Is Kikkula is based on a real lake in Canada?
Right? That was Canada. Okay, okay. By the way, I'm very worldly.
New York, New York, submitted by Mar Cenni.
Oh, please tell me I said that name right. Is this my Cenni?
So did you guys like, wait?
Calgary, oh my god!
Okay, wait, we're going to read a couple pages. So, Nendo Gura and the view from the tallest building in the United States, it was the first, oh excuse me, it was the third time I ever came back to NYC, but it will never lose its magic.
I like heights and tall buildings, so for me the number one thing is to go
to all the observatory decks for the public and taking pictures of the breathtaking skyline.
I've been here!
This big pointy building, I've been here! Yeah.
I wanted to use the bathroom at the top, tippy-tippy-top, because then I could say that I went to the bathroom in the world's tallest building,
which is not something that
current me, past me thought that was really funny.
But current me thinks that's not exactly something,
that's not a topic you bring to the dinner table.
So I didn't actually do it, so I can't actually even say that I...
Haha. I... Did you know...
Did you know that I... I've... Uh... Anyway,
the variety of different kinds of museums is fascinating and one of my favorites is
the American Museum of Natural History where I took photos with those sharks.
I've not been, I don't think I've been to the Museum of Natural History.
I don't think I'm a very good museum goer. I get really bored really easily,
which is really bad.
I need to go to like, like museums for children because they have all the stuff you can touch. If a museum has touchy stuff, then I'm fine,
but if it's just a bunch of little placards, I probably wouldn't be okay.
I'd be a little... itchy. Do I touch grass often? No.
It's good for you though. So from Calgary, Alberta,
which is Canada, did you know that? By Kildareon?
I'm so sorry. The text hurts my eyeballs. I can't really see it.
Ah, hey Gup, allow me to introduce Fish Creek Provincial Park in Calgary, Alberta, Canada, one of the largest urban parks in North America.
I feel like, I feel like I'm being chosen to popcorn read, but in school and I'm really bad at reading in front of the class.
Um, it stretches 12 miles east to west coast across the city and covers an area of around uh 5.2 square miles.
I can't visualize that. Can you give me that in uh...
How many hot dogs? How many Fenway Franks is that? How many hot dogs is that?
The park contains 62 miles of trails for walking, hiking, biking, picnicking areas, fishing spots, and even an artificial lake for swimming.
Do you mean like a man-made lake? Because calling it artificial makes it sound, that makes it sound like a swimming pool. Technically a swimming pool is an artificial...
That's an artificial body of water.
Much of the park is forested and is home to a wide variety of wildlife including at least one pack of ravenous wild Dino-Gura.
Be cautious, especially during mating season. I hear they're very unsafe. Uh, beware ravenous packs of Dino-Gura.
Look at this terrifying beasties. You don't want to get cornered by a bunch of these.
They're not particularly good at stalking, but they are very cute and can convince victims to part with their food.
Yes. Don't let them near your ankles.
Orlando... Oh wait, there's a chapters in this.
Orlando, Florida and Rosarito, Mexico. Uh, if I went to Orlando, Florida, I knew Gura liked Disney a lot, uh, yeah. Uh, so I had to take her with me on a trip to Disney. Well, almost, it's not quite Disney, but Disney Springs of Orlando instead.
We came with a group of friends for Pokemon Go event and had lots of fun catching Pokemon, eating tasty sweet treats, funny sea monsters, and seeing a fight between a dragon and a knight.
In Disney? They got medieval fights in Disney? Medieval joust fights in Disney?
Gura also tried to eat some of the fish at the Rainforest Cafe, saying "Just one tiny bite, please," with a cute face as well as meeting some of her dino ancestors at T-Rex Cafe.
Man, that is so cool that you actually brought Dino-Gura to all these places. Are you an android? Poke-fan!
Also, I didn't know people still play Pokemon Go. I thought that was uh done did and uh no longer done in 20 what was that? 20
18 or something.
But that again, when I was in Japan,
But then again, when I was in Japan,
I went to this place. I don't remember who I was with.
Oh, we went to this place, or was it Inasa?
It might have been Inasa, I don't remember.
I don't remember, but they had like the life-size Pokémon GO trainers
in this really brightly lit room. It hurt my eyes,
but it felt like I was transported to another place.
It's pretty cool.
It is pretty cool.
Uh and then Xbox went to Rosarito, Mexico.
And then Xbox went to Rosarito, Mexico.
Puerto Nuevo is a fishing village right next to the beach in Rosarito.
It's famous for serving some of the best fresh lobster in the world.
Legends say that sometimes you can spot a big fish at this location.
Oh yeah?
Which one? This one?
Listen, when we migrate, we just we end up in different places.
Listen, when we migrate, we just end up in different places.
It's just what fishies do.
We went to... Cuyadad de Mexico?
Oh my god, I wish I could pronounce these better.
Oxford, Ontario.
Wait, I see meat stick. I see flowers.
Somebody's going to be tortured medially.
Maine, Minnesota.
Massachusetts.
Oh god, dino sighting on the East Coast.
South Carolina, the Goves!
In Tennessee, are you kidding me?
There's literally a place called The Goves.
I'm getting sidetracked.
I got to keep going, but...
I love this. Thank you guys so much.
Alberta, Canada.
That's so pretty.
Look at the color of the water. It looks like my bath after I put a bath bomb in it.
It's so blue. Lake Astro?
Is it Astro or Ostra?
I'm not stupid, don't answer that.
Baja, California, Mexico.
Wait, is it Baja or Baja? See?
New York.
A la de los Santos.
Southern Maine.
Vernon, Buffalo.
Coastal dab.
And it's the it's the shark girl! I've seen her on stream before.
Chihuahua, Mexico.
New Orleans.
Oh my god! Minnesota, Hawaii...
...Illinois, Iowa...
So this means that's a bunch of people. If you guys brought out your Guras around other people,
that means that maybe like the government started tracking all these sightings.
Imagine if they really registered me as a cryptid, or not me, but technically Gura,
because people kept saying, 'Hey, what is this thing? That bitch just... these things we keep seeing everywhere.'
And now you're on a government watchlist.
Wait, pizza time.
Cute.
Europe, you guys went to Europe too?
Visiting Italy.
Brighton, England.
Oh, definitely government watchlist.
100%.
This is amazing.
I feel I feel...
I'm feeling things.
I'm getting emotional.
We have cosplayers!
We have Moon, we have Munya, we actually have Moon members' ID as well.
Thank you guys.
This is amazing.
It's like 200 postcards to me from you.
Oh my god, I went to Brazil!
I literally went to Brazil.
Thanks to you guys.
Festival!
And then there's messages.
This is where I'm going to cry.
This is this is it. This is what I'm going to do it.
I'm going to cry. I can't though because we have...
We got to we got to we got to...
We got to... we got to...
Oh my god, a tractor! Is that a John Deere?
I didn't realize how expensive these things were. John Deeres?
I don't know why. I watched the tractor comparison video
And it was like, what? Is that Danny DeVito in a shark hood?
That's amazing. Thank you guys! This is incredible.
Every year you guys spoil me so much, I just
I'm very excited, I'm very excited to read all of these. Thank you so much everyone.
Thank you so many of you. So many of you put so much work into this. Thank you!
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I do believe it's time for your goody bag, if you'll have it.
If you would like a goody bag, I have a bag of goodies for you. It's a goody bag of goodies for you.
Uh, okay. So, uh, his thank you.
So, the first uh, I'm going to open the goody bag for you.
So, don't worry. The first goody the goody bag, it is uh uh uh
Where is it?
There it is.
Well, here's the first one. Here's the first little something.
It's the Da Boing!
It's new emotes! New emotes. I don't know where to put. Oh my god.
A bit of a birthday tradition, but still, I think it's nice. We have some fresh new emotes from Mary. Thank you!
I didn't really think the uh transparent background through, did I? No.
We have an unamused Abby.
We have dino Gura.
We have, still like Elmo on fire meme.
Abby is on fire, but everything is fine. Then we have a big old thumbs up.
And I think you should be able to use them, you will use them sooner than later.
But yeah, we have some emotes just for you.
Where did I put this? Emotes? Emotes, where did I put this?
Okay, emotes. Um, oh god, I didn't I didn't think this through.
Okay, I didn't really uh I didn't really think this through.
Oh, but I hope you like the emotes and also thank you Mary for once again doing an amazing job with the emotes.
I'm sorry, I'm a scatterbrain.
Um, the next one is the big one, didn't fit in the goody bag, so I didn't really I don't um anyway,
So, do you remember a long time ago when I kind of in passing just I mentioned like uh,
Hey, wouldn't it be wouldn't it be funny if I made like a an animated a fully animated OP, but for myself?
Is that? It's all done!
And I'm freaking out. Do you want to see it?
It's all done. I didn't animate it, of course.
Don't get that idea. I didn't I didn't, it was a big team project once again.
But I we did it! Woo, and I would like to show you now.
It comes the ads and the ads and the ads and the ads and the ads.
It's pretty much what I have to say. I'm very nervous. The nerves are getting worse as I go.
So yeah, I'd like to show you that now.
Zoom!
How do I...
blublublublub
Ah!
わがままでも おっけー
Even if I'm selfish, it's okay!
ほら だって
Look, because...
あたしって 特別 (bang, bang)
I am special, bang, bang!
あらあら 泣いちゃうって
Oh my, you're gonna cry?
可愛くって かぷってしちゃうから
You're so cute, I could just take a bite!
toss out the attitude, sir
where's your thought and gratitude?
we're mad at you, so grab a few defenses
you'll be glad you're screwed
would i fight with you? wouldn't waste my time
the mood's right so this go-around the honor's all mine
no place to run, don't you ever hide
only time i wanna see you down is on ya knees, at my side!
(どうなってんのよ) 我々 こそが queen
(What's going on?) We are the queen!
(どうなってんのよ) 解らせて あげるわ
(What's going on?) I'll make you understand.
逆らう なら 痛い、痛い、ご褒美 あげましょう
If you oppose, pain, pain, I'll give you a reward!
woah-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
don't bite the hand that feeds you if it's holding a knife
still gotcha tongue tied? guess you better gimme your life
解ったら yes を 聞かせて？
Once you understand, let me hear your "yes"?
ああ 壊しちゃうたい
Ah, I want to break you,
モノにしちゃうたい
I want to make you mine,
甘い リップ の 中 で 狂って？
Go crazy inside sweet lips?
がおー 噛っ ちゃう ぞ
Roar, I'm gonna bite you!
ほら ごちゃってしてして
Hey, messing around all over,
生き たい と 何 度 も 願って？
Wishing over and over to live?
give you a " kiss ", good night
Give you a "kiss", good night,
that " prey " you 're stalking 's got bite
that "prey" you're stalking's got bite!
talkin ' shit ?
Talkin' shit?
you only exist to get pissed and fight
slow brain , no shame , what'chu gotta say now ?
Slow brain, no shame, what'chu gotta say now?
tired of the ones that were running the game ?
Tired of the ones that were running the game?
now there 's no escape , you ain't the boss of us
Now there's no escape, you ain't the boss of us,
there 's no caution tape for the monstrous
there's no caution tape for the monstrous!
it 's over , for you , ha - ha
It's over for you, ha-ha!
(どうなってんのよ) 我々 こそ が queen
(What's going on?) We are the queen!
(どうなってんのよ) 解らせて あげるわ
(What's going on?) I'll make you understand.
逆らう なら 痛い、痛い、ご褒美 あげましょう
If you oppose, pain, pain, I'll give you a reward!
woah-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
don't bite the hand that feeds you if it's holding a knife
still gotcha tongue tied? guess you better gimme your life
(どうなってんのよ) 我々 こそ が queen
(What's going on?) We are the queen!
(どうなってんのよ) 解らせて あげるわ
(What's going on?) I'll make you understand.
逆らう なら 痛い、痛い、ご褒美 あげましょう
If you oppose, pain, pain, I'll give you a reward!
woah-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
don't bite the hand that feeds you if it's holding a knife
still gotcha tongue tied? guess you better gimme your life
woah-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
you 're on the wrong side , isn't that the same way you died ?
you're on the wrong side, isn't that the same way you died?
woah-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
it 's been a long ride , we 'll reclaim the queendom tonight
it's been a long ride, we'll reclaim the queendom tonight!
解ったら yes を 聞かせて？
Once you understand, let me hear your "yes"?
わがままでも おっけー
Even if I'm selfish, it's okay,
ほら だって
look, because...
あたしって 特別 (bang, bang)
I am special, bang, bang!
あらあら 泣い ちゃう って
Oh my, you're gonna cry?
可愛くって
You're so cute,
か ぷっ てし ちゃう から
I could just take a bite!
I'm shaking.
I'm shaking and shaking and... ahh!
I really quickly would like to say a big thank you to the team that made that possible.
You're going to be seeing it a lot, so... yeah.
Okay, so I have a photo here...
A quick thank you because it would not have been possible without everybody involved here.
Of course it's myself, but we have the Hololive English team...
We have Jeruet, we have Dudul, I211, we have Beast, we have Julius, we have Anna... I'm shaking so bad!
Kyun, and we have Ruan, we have Riichu, we have Wiki, and we have Wonder...
These are the fantastic people working with Tonari. Thank you very very much, Tonari!
I am so happy to have been able to work with everybody at Tonari again. I'm such a big fan of Tonari.
I hope you enjoyed it. I did!
Maybe... maybe we watch again and go frame by frame another time...
Because there's a lot of little Easter eggs in there. That's the thing I love about Tonari is that...
they are... they're holo live fans, so they always put a lot of little, little teeny tiny holo live things...
little Easter eggs in there that you wouldn't necessarily recognize if you weren't a avid holo live fan.
little Easter eggs in there that you wouldn't necessarily recognize if you weren't an avid holo live fan.
Oh nice, you have the emotes working! That's pretty good. The thumb is very cute.
Like, for example, one of the... one of the things that caught my eye was the when I did the heart and then U was backwards from the Christmas VR chat stream...
like something like that would have probably gone over some people's heads, but... no.
Oh, also funny story, there's a part where I'm shaking my butt during the yabujabujabu...
different dances that uh I was going to do during those sections
different dances that I was going to do during those sections,
And I said, can we replace this one with me shaking my my my butt?
And I said, "Can we replace this one with me shaking my butt?"
And Tonari team was like, what do you I didn't I can't visualize that. What do you mean?
And Tanari team was like, "What do you... I can't visualize that. What do you mean?"
I said, I'm like bent over, sticking my tail in your face and I'm shaking.
And then I remembered that it was referenced from the the New Year stream and I sent that,
And then I remembered that it was referenced from the New Year stream and I sent that,
And they were like shaking your shaking your what?
Uh a what? Wait, what?
"A... what? Wait, what?"
Shaking your is it like this? And they were like, oh okay.
So just just literally you blood to the camera.
So just... just literally, you, butt to the camera.
I said, yes, exactly that.
He was very yuby, but it was very comical, very funny.
He was very yabai, but it was very comical, very funny.
I'm very, very happy. I'm very happy. I'm very nervous still.
But um... Yeah!
And there was a lot of other Hololive members in there. We had Conseil, we had Matsuri, we had...
Oh god, we had Shion, we had Ollie, who else do we have?
Matsuri and bear fart? Kanata? Toko?
Thank you, Donarari!
Um... okay, let me see. I'm just keeping up with my brain. Oh, okay.
Okay, I'm going to sing now. I just want to sing you a song because I need to calm down. We're going to karaoke now. Hope that's all right.
Is it going to be shaky? Probably. Am I a nervous birthday girl? Yeah.
What should we sing? Let's do this. I just want to sing this...
To you...
yes my love to you
私わ 私 あなたは あなたと
I am only me, you are only you,
昨夜言ってたそんな気もするわ
I said that last night and still feel the same way,
グレイのジャケットに見覚えがあるコーヒーのしみ
You in your gray jacket with that familiar coffee stain,
相変わらずなのは
Just as you always are,
ショウウィンドウに二人写れば
Our reflection in the display window,
stay with me...
真夜中のドアをたたき 帰らないと泣いた
Knocking on midnight's door, begging you not to go home,
あの季節が今目の前 stay with me...
That season when I cried right in front of your eyes, stay with me...
口ぐせを言いながら 二人の瞬間を抱いて
Saying our favorite words, holding on to our little moment,
まだ忘れず大事にしていた
I'll never forget it as long as I live.
恋と愛とは違うものよと 昨夜言われたそんな気もするわ
They say love and affection are two different things you told me last night,
二度目の冬が来て 離れていたあなたの心 振り向けばいつもそこにあなたを感じていたの
Winter comes again and your heart has gone away, if I look back I see that I could always feel you by my side,
stay with me...
真夜中のドアをたたき 心に穴があいた
Knocking on midnight's door, there's a hole in my heart,
あの季節が今目の前 stay with me...
That season when I cried right in front of your eyes, stay with me...
淋しさまぎらせて 置いたレコードの針 同じメロディー繰り返していた
Distracted by my loneliness, the needle on my record player was stuck on a repeating melody,
stay with me...
真夜中のドアをたたき 帰らないと泣いた
Knocking on midnight's door, begging you not to go home,
あの季節が今目の前 stay with me...
That season when I cried right in front of your eyes, stay with me...
口ぐせを言いながら 二人の瞬間を抱いて
Saying our favorite words, holding on to our little moment,
まだ忘れず大事にしていた
I'll never forget how warm it felt.
恋と愛とは違うものよと
They say love and affection are two different things,
昨夜言われたそんな気もするわ 二度目の冬が来て 離れていたあなた 心
You told me last night, sometimes I think so too. Winter comes again and your heart has gone away,
振り向けばいつもそこにあなたを感じていたの
If I look back I see that I could always feel you by my side,
stay with me... 真夜中のドアをたたき 心に穴があいた
Stay with me... Knocking on midnight's door, there's a hole in my heart...
あの季節が
That season...
いま目の前で Stay with me
is right before my eyes now, stay with me...
寂しさ紛らわして
Distracting my loneliness,
追いかけて 心の針
chasing after the needle of my heart.
同じメロディ 繰り返ししていた
Repeating the same melody over and over...
あの季節が いま目の前で Stay with me
That season is right before my eyes now, stay with me...
口ぐせを言いながら
Uttering my favorite phrase,
二人の瞬間を抱いて まだ忘れず温めていた
I embraced our moments together, still remembering and keeping them warm.
あの季節が いま目の前で Stay with me
That season is right before my eyes now, stay with me...
迷い仲のドアを叩き
Knocking on midnight's door,
帰れないと泣いた
crying that I can't go home.
あの季節が いま目の前で Stay with me
That season is right before my eyes now, stay with me...
打ち寄せる波を見ながら 2人の時間を抱いて
Looking at the crashing waves, holding our time together...
まだ忘れず温めていた Stay with me
Still remembering and keeping them warm, stay with me...
迷い仲のドアを叩き
Knocking on midnight's door,
帰れないと泣いた
crying that I can't go home.
あの季節が いま目の前で Stay with me
That season is right before my eyes now, stay with me...
I'm gonna miss you so much!
Who is that?
Interrupting my karaoke.
What do you want?
What do you want, you little red devil?
What are you doing here?
Do you want this thing?
Why is it standing there? Why isn't it saying anything? Why does it look like that?
Wasn't a big enough budget to get you in 3D, huh?
Oh.
Looks like the poor little red gura has to stay behind.
Uh-oh.
Uh-oh, spaghetti-o.
You want what?
You want to battle me in karaoke?
How are you going to do that when you look like flat Stanley?
Somebody better have a balloon pump,
'cause I'm winning just by being 3D.
You still want to battle me? Okay.
What do you guys think? Should we battle the red gura in karaoke?
What did you say?
Did you hear that?
He said he's cuter than me.
What do you mean you're cuter than me?
I'm cute!
I am Gura! This is so cuter than me!
I'm Gura! This is so cuter than me!
Prove it! What do you mean, prove it?
I can prove it!
I can prove it, but we're going to have to step up the game, I think.
I think I want to squish this little challenger even flatter than they already are. Are you hear me?
I think I want to squish this little challenger even flatter than they already are. Do you hear me?
You little red flat thing.
Let me get ready.
I'm bringing the big guns of cute, okay?
Give me two seconds. I'll be back.
You're going to eat it,
you little shard-stained, yeah.
you little shark-stained... yeah.
語れない 眠れない トロイメライ
An unspeakable, sleepless daydream...
あなたの見てる正体
the true nature of what you're seeing.
誰も読めない カルト
A carte that no one can read,
不思議 知りたいだけ
I just want to know the wonder of it.
嘘も現実も どっちも真実だったの 本当よ
Both lies and reality were both true in the end, really.
今日もひとりごと
Today as well, talking to myself,
なににも無理をしないで わたし愛されたい
without pushing myself too hard, I just want to be loved.
有無有::*; さようなら 軽い眩暈
Yes or no, goodbye, a light dizziness...
ひとりごと
A soliloquy...
何も無理はしないで
Don't push yourself too hard.
私 愛されたい
I want to be loved.
もやもや さようなら 軽い目眩
Gloom and doom, farewell, a slight dizziness.
あなたのいない化粧会
A makeup session without you...
誰も読めないカルテ 知識溢れ出して
A chart no one can read, knowledge overflowing.
鼓動を 世界中が
My heartbeat, the whole world...
いつも 噛み合わないの
Is always out of sync.
いたくて
It hurts,
まいよ ねがいごと
Oh, my wish...
何も 歌いたわなくて
Having nothing left to sing,
混ざり溶け合いたい
I want to blend and melt together.
かわいげない 分からない 強気存在
Uncute, incomprehensible, strong presence.
あなたと の家族を 壊したい
I want to break our family...
新しい夢は
My new dream is...
悲しい声は
A sad voice,
美しい 疑わしい 羨ましいね
Beautiful, suspicious, how envious.
どれ語れない 護れない 揃いめらい
None can be told, none can be protected, hesitation aligned.
あなたの 見てる勝負っ気
The competitive spirit you're looking at...
誰も読めないカルテ 不思議知りたいただけ
A chart no one can read, I just want to know the mystery.
終わらない 言葉ない 揃いめらい
Endless, wordless, hesitation aligned.
あなたと またのきょうをかい
Meeting you again today...
青春 みずぐちまねの うち 不思議知りたいただけ
Youth, mimicking water's edge... I just want to know the mystery.
私じゃ私のことを愛して何がわるいの
What's wrong with loving myself?
嫉妬でしょうか 痛いだとか
Is it jealousy? Calling me pathetic or weird,
変わってる手とか届きませんね
none of that reaches me.
そのリプレイ 大好きな御召物
That replay, my favorite outfit,
大好きなメイクでお出かけしよう
let's go out with my favorite makeup.
日傘持って飛び出だせ 幸せだもん
Grab a parasol and rush out, because I'm happy.
チュッ！かわいくてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute.
生まれてきちゃってごめん
Sorry for being born this way.
チュッ！気安くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so approachable.
努力しちゃってごめん
Sorry for putting in the effort.
チュッ！お洒落でごめん
Chu! Sorry for being fashionable.
女子力高くてごめん ムカついちゃうよねざまあ！
Sorry for having such high girlish charm, tough luck!
あなたはあなたのことだけどうぞ私に関係しないで
Mind your own business, don't interfere with me.
Well, 不安な夜の動物・マーケットで
Well, in the animal market of an uneasy night,
価値観の暗がりでパンチマイム
doing mime in the darkness of values,
時限爆弾 ドン 唸ってる僕らの限りある魂よ
ticking time bombs, bang, our limited souls are roaring—
get down! Get down!
Well, 生産性のまるでおかしい猿
Well, like a totally absurd monkey of productivity,
縛られた脳no thank you
a bound brain, no thank you.
危険信号 どうなったって知りやしない
Danger signal, I don't care what happens,
限りある可能性だ Yeah!
it's limited potential, yeah!
植え付けてきた思い込みすら
Even the preconceptions that were planted
締め付けているいばらのようで
feel like thorns tightening around us.
回る少年 浮かぶ泣き顔
A spinning boy with a floating tearful face—
「噛み付くぜ今は苦しいけど」って笑った
he smiled, saying, "I'll bite back, even if it hurts right now."
走った 中毒性の激しい淡い恋
Running through a pale love with intense addiction,
漁られたの 怖いほど
being searched through until it's terrifying.
危険信号 どうなったっていいんじゃない
Danger signal, wouldn't it be fine whatever happens?
限りある可能性だ
It's limited potential.
植え付けられた深い仕草で
With deeply planted gestures
締め付けられていばらのように
tightening like thorns,
変わる少女 浮かぶ目覚めた目
a changing girl with a floating, awakened gaze—
噛み付く夜
biting through the night.
今は狂えばいい
It's fine to go mad now.
白む自尊心 歪みサスティナー
Fading self-esteem, distorted sustainer,
千セカンズも不可能が纏わり付いていた
a thousand seconds clung to by the impossible.
ハロー聴こえているハロー
Hello, can you hear me? Hello,
当たり前の境に立っている
standing at the boundary of the ordinary.
かさばる自意識歪んでく
My bulky self-consciousness distorts.
不安な夜の動物・マーケットで
In the animal market of an uneasy night,
価値観の暗がりでパンチマイム
doing mime in the darkness of values,
時限爆弾 ドン 唸ってる僕らの
ticking time bombs, bang, our roaring
限りある魂よ
limited souls—
Well, 生産性のまるでおかしい猿
Well, like a totally absurd monkey of productivity,
縛られた脳no thank you
a bound brain, no thank you.
危険信号 どうなったって知りやしない
Danger signal, I don't care what happens,
限りある可能性だ
it's limited potential.
Yeah, fine, that was cute.
That was fine.
Whatever.
I was cute too.
Weren't I?
眠れない 揃いまい もろみみゃあみゃあ
Can't sleep, all matched up, moromi meow meow~
Am I going to get shown up in my own birthday stream?
Okay, fine, whatever. If you... whatever, I still have a trick up my sleeve.
You've seen me be cute.
What about a taste of cool? Can you do cool, you little red snot?
Alright, fine. You want some cool, Gura? I'll do cool, Gura.
Cool power activate!
I have copied you
And made up myself so crash and splash
I fight with my obsession
I feel the tension, a need for caution
I would like to show
I would like to show—
Cut open my skull, look into my head
I don't know why I'm so harsh
I could be so brash and go into clash
'Cause I feel
I can always show my everything to you
If this moment was for me
I try to hear, lend my ear
Voices inside, one link to join it all
All the things I knew
The world I trusted would be the same
If I remained inside my protective castle
One word brings another
My reflection in the water says to me
"Oh my god, you're such a bad shark"
Her terrifying gaze, her glowing red eyes
Begins to sink into the void at the bottom of the sea
Why (Your tired eyes)
Do you cry? (Begin to fall)
I gave you everything you craved
Tell me if (Your darkest thoughts)
I can ever be (Unleash them all)
The me you wanted me to be
No lies, but no truths either (Ah, ah)
Isn't it easier to never say what you really mean?
But someday (A time and place)
Somewhere (For darker days)
Will we find someplace to understand each other?
Look at this so-called "gem of the sea"
Odd and scrawny, you see what I mean?
Return to what you know, it ain't much I know
Heh, it shows
I'm not like you
Stop it, I hate the way you judge me (I hate it)
I don't need to conform to any ideals
I just want to be myself
Just want to be understood
Heh! If you don't conform, then why were you even born?
There are no hopes, no dreams, just pain, pain, pain, pain
Be yourself? Do you even know who you are?
Give it up and just ride the waves
Just chill
I've been searching and searching, and found my own answer
I won't lie to myself anymore
I'm sorry
(One story ends)
All this time
(Begin again)
I've been too blind to see
I'm only here this way
(While hand-in-hand)
Because of you
(Until the end)
Because you've been there by my side
The past isn't important? That's not true
(Ah, ah)
A life that's unpredictable is so much brighter
From here on out
(No matter where)
Just watch quietly
(Watch over me)
How I live my life
So, you think that's all, huh?
Just gonna leave like it's nothing?
Going without me?
(I don't know what you're thinking!)
Return to the sea
A shark is all you'll ever be
Farewell
(Our story ends)
Thank you
(Begin again)
I won't hide my heart's desires anymore
Farewell
(Once hand-in-hand)
Thank you
(Until the end)
I'll accept my everything and live
The bottom of the sea is a boring place
(Ah, ah)
But I'll keep you in my thoughts forever
No matter when
(No matter where)
No matter where
(Watch over me)
I'll live life true to myself
Nothing bad is without something good
波打ち際 ほほどけた 髪 帽子の 先
At the water's edge, untied hair, tip of the hat
見覚え ある 青い ワーゲン stop the flashback
Feels familiar, blue Volkswagen, stop the flashback
南風の (in southern winds) いたずらな 魔法ね (it’s magic rays)
In the southern winds, mischievous magic, it's magic rays
遠い 夏 の あの 眩暈に 戻さ ないで (be with you)
Don't take me back to that distant summer dizziness, be with you
again
maybe love, stray my heart
なきぬけ 顔 を し て キス を 奪って don't go away
With a casual expression, stealing a kiss, don't go away
今 だけ は 寄り添って あげるわ
Just for now, I'll snuggle up to you
唇 に ぬくもり 残し て close to you
Leaving warmth on your lips, close to you
肩すくめて ボンネット から 腰あげて
Shrugging shoulders, lifting hips from the bonnet
語りすぎ よ 飽きてき たわ stay the flashlight
Talking too much, getting tired, stay the flashlight
似た 人 みたい (so look alike) 解きかかけた 魔法ね (fade-in, fade-out)
Looking like someone else, the fading magic, fade-in, fade-out
遠い夏 の あの 眩暈に 戻り たい の (be with you) no more
I want to go back to that distant summer dizziness, be with you, no more
maybe love, stray my heart
さりげない しぐさ を し て キス を そらす わ i go away
With a casual gesture, avoiding the kiss, I go away
夕立に 付き合う 気 ない から
I don't feel like sticking around for the evening shower
崩れてく オンショア 波 の まにま に turnaround
As the onshore crumbles, at the mercy of the waves, turnaround
maybe love, stray my heart
何もかも 蜃気楼
Everything is a mirage
夏 の 女神 の 気まぐれ ね
The whims of the summer goddess
いつか また だ なんて i never say
Someday, I'll never say 'again'
唇 に うらはら 残し た まま で turnaround
Leaving a grudge on your lips, as it is, turnaround
あれ が 船 出 た だよう
There goes a ship setting sail
香り 残っ た 牙 が 笑わ ない で
A lingering scent, don't laugh with your fangs showing
あぁ来てみて
Ah, come see
セクシー世界一スーパーピチピチぶっちゃけ調子づかまええたくない
Sexiest in the world, super fresh and youthful
やっぱりゲットザトレジャーメイビテイステイングミー
You want the treasure? Maybe you're tasting me
私との甘さが欲しいテショ
Do you want my sweetness?
あぁ来てみて ちょっとヴォーリィ！ 秘宝の国を
Ah, come see, hey vault! To the land of hidden treasure
あぁ来てみて ちょっとヴォーリィ！ 優しくして
Ah, come see, hey vault! Treat me gently
あぁ来てみて ちょっとヴォーリィ！ 本当この扉
Ah, come see, hey vault! Truly this door
あぁ来てみて マジで早かけて
Ah, come see, run away fast
しれーたいあなたの手
Knowing your hand
返すりごもさまいづめいきのち
Returning like a flash, full of life
じぇ
Yeah
ハッピーシンセサイザ 君の胸の奥まで
Happy synthesizer, reaching deep into your heart,
届くようなメロディ 奏でるよ
I'll play a melody for you.
僅か散った淡い片思い
Remembered a fragile, fading unrequited love—
笑い話だね 今となれば
It's all a funny story when we look back.
見る物全て 輝いて見えた
Everything we saw seemed to shine brightly,
あの日々がキレイに 笑ってるよ
Those days are smiling at us so cleanly.
我慢する事だけ 覚えなきゃいけないの?
Do we only need to learn to hold back our feelings?
「大人になって頂戴ね?」ならなくていいよ
"Grow up to be an adult, okay?" We don't have to be.
知らない事ばかり 知らないなんて言えなくて
There are so many things I don't know, but I can't admit it,
「大変お似合いで」 ウソついてゴメンね
"You two make a lovely pair," sorry for the lie.
ハッピーシンセサイザ 君の胸の奥まで
Happy synthesizer, reaching deep into your heart,
届くようなメロディ 奏でるよ
I'll play a melody for you.
つまらない「たてまえ」や やな事全部
All those boring excuses and unpleasant things,
消してあげるから この音で
I'll make them all disappear with this sound.
何の取り柄もない 僕に唯一できる事
The only thing I can do, with no special talents,
少しだけど 出来る事
Just a little something I can manage.
心躍らせる 飾らない 言葉
Unadorned words that make your heart leap,
電子音で伝えるよ
I'll convey them with electronic sound.
好きになる事 理屈なんじゃなくて
Falling in love isn't about reason or logic,
「こじつけ」なんて いらないんじゃない?
You don't need any far-fetched excuses, right?
時代のせいと 諦めたらそこまで
If you blame the times and give up, that's the end of it,
踏み出さなくちゃ何も始まらない
If you don't take a step forward, nothing begins.
「ゴメンね夜遅く 眠るところだったでしょ?」
"Sorry to call so late, were you going to sleep?"
「驚いた 私もかけようとしてた」
"I'm surprised, I was just about to call you too."
心の裏側を くすぐられてるような
It's like the back of our hearts are being tickled,
惹かれあう2人に 幸せな音を
Wishing happy music for the two drawn together.
ハッピーシンセサイザ ほらね 楽しくなるよ
Happy synthesizer, see? It gets so fun!
涙拭うメロディ 奏でるよ
I'll play a melody to wipe away tears.
強がらなくたっていいんじゃない? 別に
It's okay not to act so tough, you know.
自分に素直になれればいい
As long as you can be honest with yourself.
何の取り柄もない 僕に唯一できる事
The only thing I can do, with no special talents,
少しだけど 出来る事
Just a little something I can manage.
Okay, thank you, Mori!
I mean, it's my birthday!
I want right now.
I want it right now.
You can't wear me right now.
Okay, fair enough, fair enough.
A little red, a little where are you? Come on, you can join the stream now.
A little red, a little—where are you? Come on, you can join the stream now.
You've been nice enough.
You did fine! You did great!
Whatever, we're really pulling out treasure box? Okay, I see how it is. Fine.
Whatever, we're really pulling out a treasure box? Okay, I see how it is. Fine.
...whatever you want to do, really.
It'll help you clean up.
I desperately need these because I am the number one culprit of
of cable spaghetti.
They're cute though, they have Ebi and Bloop on them.
And they're blue, the most important part.
gurED versus BLUeRa Glass Set
featuring today's competition...
Red Gura. Red Gura versus BLUeRa.
Whose side are you on?
Whose side are you on? Is this going to be like a twilight thing all over?
Whose side are you on? Is this going to be like a Twilight thing?
No, because at the end of the day, Gura is Gura. And Gura Q...
No, because at the end of the day, Gura is Gura, and Gura Q—
ish. Planet is a little bit... Team BLUeRa.
They're cute though, they're by Sakomiyanko!
And it might be hard to see from the stream,
but if you zoom in, the red, the red shark and stuff has like an angry face, and then the blue shark has a cute, happy face. It's really cute.
Yeah, you can drink the blood of your enemies, or your morning strawberry smoothie, whatever you desire.
And then the item that I am most excited about, that I... I... I am so excited about this, that...
And then the item that I am most excited about, that I... I'm so excited about this, that...
He's real. Ebi-chan is real!
You can get your hands on a big, fat Ebi-chan, perfect for squeezing. He's pocket-sized.
Or as I like to compare it, Ebi-chan here is about the size of a healthy dill pickle. A whole dill pickle.
And I scribbled my name on the bottom just so you remember.
I mean, you could put your name on it if you really wanted to, but I put my name on it. I guess that technically means you're mine.
I can share though. We have Ebi-chan. I want to get a bunch and stack them on top of each other.
Yeah, he's like the perfect size to grip tightly in your hands so you can use him as a stress ball if you want. Or you can... I don't know, hit it with a baseball bat...
Or... I don't know, whatever. If you need a little bit of pocket motivation, he'll fit in your pocket, if you'll have him. Or on top of your head, like me.
Thank you, Ebi-chan. Put it in a jar. You don't have to put it in... I mean, you could, but...
I would put Red Gura in the jar before I put Ebi-chan in the jar. Ebi doesn't deserve it. Ebi doesn't deserve being put in the jar.
No, Chad, no! No, my lovelies, please think before you act. What has this poor creature done to you?
What if he's too heavy and you can't even support his front side? You wouldn't put a creature like that in a jar.
You must nurture him and caress his tall antenna and make cute heart shapes with him and send pictures to me.
Fry it? It's going to taste like polyester and copper. Mmm, tasty.
Put some butter on that. Ah, you can caress... You can caress the Ebi gently though, he's very sensitive.
They're a sensitive crustacean. I purple take Gura, thank you.
Yummy yummy. Nani? Yummy copper. No, don't put... don't put it in your mouths. It's not meant for your mouth.
Your mouth hole. I love this little combo you guys can do now with the Ebi. The Ebi thumbs up affirmation, the thump... the thump up affirmation Ebi emote is very cute. You is this one? I like it.
Let's see what else. And we're going to be doing illustration. Thank you, thank you. Shi... Shiino-san, thank you.
I'm going to be hand-signing again. Let's everybody say a prayer that I can actually spell my name correctly for those of you that got my incorrectly spell uh name last time, I apologize.
I'm going to be hand-signing again. Let's everybody say a prayer that I can actually spell my name correctly. For those of you that got my incorrectly spelled name last time, I apologize.
Um... but hey, now you have now you have proof that I am a dum-dum and physical proof. But yeah, we're going to be doing some more signing. Shoo, shoo, shoo, shoo, shoo. And try really hard not to... yeah, spell the name wrong. Also, oh never mind, I probably shouldn't say that one.
Yay, though! And as a bonus for limited edition, so those are limited. I hate to say that, but they are limited.
Unfortunately for now,
maybe someday I'll just be able to give out
whatever... whatever everblooming ones in unlimited quantities.
The unlimited quant... is there spelling mistakes?
They always ask me, they sometimes they ask me, they're like, "Hey Gura, can you can you guess this for or can you look up this for spelling mistakes?" And I say, "Yeah."
And then I don't really do it because I am the worst person to do that with. Please don't ask me for that.
It's sold out. Is it actually sold out, or is it just the website having to update?
Cuz that that's the thing that happens with like merchandise websites is that they usually just go, "Oh, it's sold out," but it just takes some of it.
Is it not... is it actually?
I don't think actually sold out.
It's gone, why?
Boo.
Limited is sold out?
I'm so sorry.
Well, um, I'm going to hold that hope that the website is... is being smelly. The website's being smelly.
Well, um, maybe maybe I know, I'll pull management side and I'll say,
"Because I'm the birthday girl, as my birthday girl wish, I would like to ensure that everybody gets exactly what they want."
As... since I am the birthday girl, I therefore was like everybody else to be a birthday person and get their birthday wish as well.
Yeah, let's see if that passes.
Pretty please? I have a thing of sprinkles right here.
Cuz I eat them. I just
eat sprinkles out of the jar. Pretty please with sprinkles on top?
Pretty please?
Boobodiboodiboodiboo!
Hey, birthday!
Why? Because you guys remember when I used to drink maple syrup right out of the jar?
I used to do that.
For those of you that don't know, I used to have a jar of uh sugar-free maple syrup that had like a baby bottle nozzle on the top.
And I would just pop it open and take like a slurrp from between the stream or something. Like, "Ooh, yummy!
Mmm, maple syrup, mmm."
If only I had a mouthful of butter.
Isn't it too sweet? No, not at all.
Yeah, it's like baby food. Well, no, I wouldn't give
I wouldn't give a baby sugar-free maple syrup.
I'm just a big baby, that's all.
A baby bottle pop of maple syrup and yummies.
Oh, oh, oh, thank you guys! Thank you everybody!
Thank you for making this an amazing birthday. A very, very amazing birthday.
Also, it's kind of funny the seeming was originally for my birthday like blues and and and yellows and cozy like that, but then last minute I was like, "I need pink."
I require pink and yellow and purple and polka dots and a cute birthday hat with cupcakes and like really cute everything and sparkles and stuff.
It's kind of... I don't know, I think that's kind of funny. Oh well, still cute though.
Still cute though.
Should we let Stinky out of the jar? Do you think she's been behaved?
I have her labeled as Red Devil in my in my stream. Let's let you out.
I'll let you out just this once since you
you can come and hang out with everybody.
Oh, you're so cute when you're up close!
Wow.
That's pretty cool. Sorry, she's talking to me, but you can't hear her.
Trust me, she's talking to me. Little goblin.
Little goblin with a little tiny little thing, little I don't know, little baby.
Well, baby says she wants to sing another song. Is she whispering an evil... No, no, no, she wants to sing some more because she's feeling very proud of herself for winning,
winning over winning over the chat.
Winning, she says, just been winning.
Superior song choices. Okay, okay, okay.
We can sing one more song together.
What do you guys think?
An encore!
The winner was chat. Chat wins all along. Everybody wins. Everybody a winner.
I like the everybody a winner.
Should we do an encore? Stinky, smelly, little fishy?
Yeah?
Should we do it together? I think we should do a song together. What do you think?
I think that would be cute.
I think that would be a cute... uh reminder that at the end of the day, we're
all in
let's get together
God, I'm so awkward.
Maybe you should take over, red Gura, because then maybe you won't be as awkward as I am. This is painful.
Maybe you should take over, red Gura, because maybe you won't be as awkward as I am. This is painful.
We're gonna go ahead. We're gonna go ahead and sing something.
We'll figure it out behind the scenes, because I I know where we're gonna sing. I know exactly where we're gonna sing.
We'll figure it out behind the scenes, 'cause I know where we're gonna sing. I know exactly where we're gonna sing.
Okay, you ready? Gu... Gu... Gu... ah, okay, she's ready.
A-encore! A-encore! A-encore! A-encore!
Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore!
Always keep your eyes on the line of the horizon
Come on chumbuds, climb on-board and set sail to brighter days!
yay!
a-a, a-a, a-a, aa-a-a
a-a, aa-a-a
Waves will knock you down
and currents pull you out, a-a
Life hits her with the ol' "hoo-cha!"
Tryna make a splash but every stream has crashed
oh nyo!
But still we keep on swimming
Jabu-jabu jabu, jabu-jabu
Chouten hoshoku-sha, suichu haishin-sha
Shrimp in' everyday
Shrimp-in' everyday
Zabu-zabu zabu, zabu-zabu, suima dayo, uki wa fuyo
bisho bisho
It's almost time, just gimme a sec!
Nine thousand years gives you a crick in the neck
With a hand to hold, we're not alone
Got a heart of gold and a head of bone
No one panic, we've just begun
Bein' hydrodynamic, it's just more fun
So hang on bloop 'cause the water's rough
You can't spell "guratsuku" without "gura"!
Come sail away with me
Our future's beyond the sea
The sunrise shine on our lives
There's no dream we can't reach
So no matter how we grow, just always know
I'm the same same desu!
Always keep your eyes on the line of the horizon
Come on chumbuds, climb on-board and set sail to brighter days!
A!
Okay, everybody...
thanks for my birthday stream of 2023.
Woohoo!
Yeah!
I hope you enjoyed your time today with me.
Thank you very much for spending time with me and for saying hey after all this time.
I really appreciate it. I hope you had fun. I hope you were entertained, even just a little bit.
I hope, uh, I hope your days are going well and your and your life is going well, honestly.
I hope, uh, I hope your days are going well and your life is going well, honestly.
Um, thank you so much again for the support. I hope you enjoy everything that I've showed you today.
You know, I every- everybody that has helped to make today's stream possible, thank you very much.
Everybody that has helped to make today's stream possible, thank you very much.
Thank you thank you thank you, and thank you to, uh, Manet-san as well for helping me through all of this, I really appreciate it.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, and thank you to Manet-san as well for helping me through all of this, I really appreciate it.
We have more fun stuff coming in the summer. There's a big summer, you guys. I hope you're strapped in and ready.
Strapping buttercups, it's gonna be a big one. Uh, I'm very excited, and you should be too.
Yahooh! Also, there might be another bigger...
...Goomba's 3D live on the horizon, perhaps, you may have...
It'll probably be quite a bit of ways from now, but just so you know, just another thing to look forward to.
A-wahoo! Yippee, yippee, yippee! Thank you though, guys. I'm excited.
Thank you as always. Thank you for ever. Thank you as always and forever. I'll see you around, okay?
Thank you as always. Thank you forever. Thank you as always and forever. I'll see you around, okay?
Happy birthday to me and to any of you if it's your birthday. Happy birthday.
I'm sweating. Thank you, guys. I hope you had a lovely day.
I will see you... trying to think of like a fun ocean word... I'll see you in the... in the ocean. I'll see you...
I will see you... trying to think of like a fun ocean word... I'll see you in the ocean. I'll see you...
Anyway, at least... no, sounds bad.
Uh... See you.
Happy birthday to me!
グッバイ グッバグッバグッバ... グッバイ！
Goodbye, goodbye goodbye goodbye... Goodbye!
Say bye, little girl.
She said... Oh, I can't repeat that.
バイ！
Bye!
Say bye, Gura! Say bye, Gura!
バイバイ... バイバイバイバイバイバイ...
Bye-bye... Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye...
バイ... ハー...
Bye... Ha...